fitbrains.com 2016-06-29

# This is the Fit Brains Privacy Policy.

We at Rosetta Stone Ltd ("Rosetta Stone") know you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. By using or accessing the Fit Brains products and Services (the "Services") in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we gather when you are accessing or using our Services, but not to the practices of companies we don’t own or control, or people that we don’t manage. We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained in more detail below, and we use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Services, including to personalize, provide, and improve our Services, to allow you to set up a user account and profile, to contact you and allow other users to contact you, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to analyze how you use the Services. In certain cases, we may also share some Personal Information with third parties, but only as described below.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at contact@fitbrains. com.

Children under 13 may not disclose personal information about themselves to us, but Parents or Teachers may disclose certain personal information about their Child on the Services. Such information disclosed is considered Personal Information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy. By signing up your Child, you certify that you are a Parent or Teacher who is legally authorized to register his or her Child for the Rosetta Stone Fit Brains Services. As the Parent or Teacher providing consent to your Child’s use of the Services, you agree to be bound by this Agreement in respect of your Child’s use of the Services and are solely responsible for your Child’s use of the Services. You represent and warrant that you have the authority to agree to these Terms on your Child’s behalf. You also certify that you are legally permitted to use and access the Services and take full responsibility for the selection and use of and access to the Services.

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. However, we may share your Personal Information with third parties as described in this section:

Aggregated Personal Information that’s no longer personally identifiable

As previously discussed in more detail above, we may anonymize your Personal Information so that you are not individually identified, and provide that information to our partners. We may also provide aggregate usage information to our partners, who may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Services, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience.

We also reserve the right to use non-personal information (e.g., de-identified or aggregate data) for any purpose. We may disclose performance statistics to collaborators from post-secondary institutions (i.e. universities, colleges) to evaluate, study, and improve the effectiveness of our programs or human cognition more generally. In these situations, all data is disclosed either in aggregate form or with information that can identify you removed. In addition, when we work with collaborators, we contractually prohibit them from attempting to re-identify individuals from data that has been de-identified.

Outside the United States Consent to Processing and Transfer of Information

If you access the Services outside of the United States, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in the United States.

## Agents

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you; for example, we may use a payment processing company to receive and process your credit card transactions for us. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

## Cookies

This site requires the use of cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you'll find cookies at most major web sites. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web site and is stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are used on this site to enhance the user experience.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message at contact@fitbrains. com, and we will do our best to address your concerns.

## Changes in the privacy policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. If we make material changes, we will provide advance notice to you either by email, by posting a notification on the Fit Brains website or by posting an updated Terms of Service ("TOS") on the Fit Brains website at least 45 days in advance of the effective date of the updated TOS. Please note that, for existing users, unless otherwise provided by applicable law, your continued use of the Services following the effective date of the updated TOS means that you agree with, and consent to be bound by, the updated TOS.
